{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"1311","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1312","question":"\u0d32\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1313","question":"\u0d24\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1314","question":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1315","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d23\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d25\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1316","question":"\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1317","question":"\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d32\u0d35\u0d23\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d32\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1318","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d38\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16 ?","answer":"\u0d13\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1319","question":"\u0d2e\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1320","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d30\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e "},{"q_number":"1321","question":"\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d08\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1322","question":"\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d1a\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d24\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"1323","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d48 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"0.03 %"},{"q_number":"1324","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d48 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1325","question":"\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d33\u0d02\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32"},{"q_number":"1326","question":"\u0d07\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1327","question":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d32\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"1328","question":"\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d48 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"1329","question":"\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d7d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"1330","question":"\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1331","question":"\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1332","question":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d48\u0d38\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1333","question":"\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1334","question":"\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a"},{"q_number":"1335","question":"\u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d35\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d7e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1336","question":"\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1337","question":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1338","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d39\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1339","question":"\u0d2d\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d24\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1340","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d7e\u0d2b\u0d7c \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1341","question":"\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1342","question":"\u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1343","question":"\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d25\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1344","question":"\u0d18\u0d28 \u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1345","question":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1346","question":"\u0d24\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d24\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1347","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d7e\u0d2b\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1348","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1349","question":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d7e\u0d2b\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1350","question":"\u0d0e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2b\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1351","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d08\u0d24\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d7e "},{"q_number":"1352","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d40\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"1353","question":"\u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1354","question":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d57\u0d21\u0d7c \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d39\u0d48\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1355","question":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1356","question":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d32\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1357","question":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1358","question":"\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1359","question":"\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7d \u0d31\u0d42\u0d25\u0d7c\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1360","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"7.40"},{"q_number":"1361","question":"\u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"7.0"},{"q_number":"1362","question":"\u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d47\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e ____ \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 .","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d35\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1363","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 7-\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7e ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e ( \u0d06\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e )"},{"q_number":"1364","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"5"},{"q_number":"1365","question":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"5.5"},{"q_number":"1366","question":"\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"6"},{"q_number":"1367","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"6.5 - 6.7"},{"q_number":"1368","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 7-\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d35 ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1369","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7b\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1370","question":"\u0d31\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d33\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d7a "},{"q_number":"1371","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1372","question":"\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d7e\u0d2b\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1373","question":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1374","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d7a "},{"q_number":"1375","question":"\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1376","question":"\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1377","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a"},{"q_number":"1378","question":"\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1379","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1380","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"1381","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d33"},{"q_number":"1382","question":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d33"},{"q_number":"1383","question":"\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d35 ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ,\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1384","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02","answer":"\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d4d ( \u0d35\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d02 )"},{"q_number":"1385","question":"\u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d23\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1386","question":"\u0d30\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ____ \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 .","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e "},{"q_number":"1387","question":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1388","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1389","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d02 ,\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f ,\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1390","question":"\u0d24\u0d46\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d38\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1391","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1392","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1393","question":"\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1394","question":"\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ,\u0d08\u0d2f\u0d02 ,\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d02 ,\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f ,\u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1395","question":"\u0d2c\u0d7e\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7a "},{"q_number":"1396","question":"\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1397","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d36\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1398","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d25\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d18\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d35?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ,\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a"},{"q_number":"1399","question":"\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1400","question":"\u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d48 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1401","question":"\u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d38\u0d02\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d37\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1402","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b 78%"},{"q_number":"1403","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1404","question":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d17\u0d43\u0d39\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a\u0d21\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1405","question":"\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a\u0d21\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1406","question":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1407","question":"\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"4 \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1408","question":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1409","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d23\u0d35 \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 "},{"q_number":"1410","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2d\u0d35 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"1411","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 235"},{"q_number":"1412","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d35 ?","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 234 ,235 ,238"}]},"code":"100"}